

WORK EXPERIENCE

3 Years, 7 Month(s)
Ticketmaster(Oct 2022
- Present), Webonise Lab
(May 2021 - Oct 2022),
Akaruilabs India (March
2019 - April 2021)

AGE

25

ANKUR GUPTA

+91 8707573399 / www.roundrobin.in

ankur11.kmr@gmail.com

n linkedin.com/in/its-ankur-gupta

ABOUT ME

I am Senior Software Engineer at **Ticketmaster India**. I am a dedicated, organized, and methodical individual. I have good interpersonal skills, am keen and very willing to learn and develop new skills. My primary skills are Ruby on Rails and ReactJS. I have skills in Java Spring, Hibernate, MongoDB and Blockchain technologies. I have also qualified **Graduation Aptitude Test of Engineering (GATE) CSE** examination in **2019**. I always open to learn new technologies and have worked on multiple projects of different stacks. I have worked on Jenkins, Heroku and Netlify for deployment purpose and have experience working with AWS cloud service. Github links are as follows https://github.com/mr-ankur, https://github.com/ankur-11

Education

Qualification	College	University/Board	Passing Year
B.Tech(CSE)	Bansal Institute of Engineering and Technology	AKTU , Lucknow	2018
Intermediate	D P S S Inter College	UP Board	2014
High School	D P S S Inter College	UP Board	2012

Professional Training

- AWS Cloud Practitioner Essentials from AWS Training and Certification
- 6 weeks Training of Java Technologies at CDAC Mohali ,Punjab
- 4 weeks Training of Core Java at Cetpa InfoTech Pvt Ltd Lucknow, UP
- Personality Development Program By ZITA at Bansal Institute of Engineering and Technology Lucknow

Project Work

Title	Technology	Database	Tools Used	My Role
TEAMED GLOBAL	Ruby on Rails, ReactJS, MongoDB, CSS, HTML	Postgres Database	Git, Heroku, Postgres Database, Netlify, Terminal	Senior Software Developer
NFHS	Ruby on Rails, JQuery, Haml, CSS, HTML	Postgres Database	NGINX, AWS, Git, Jenkins, Docker, Terminal	Senior Software Developer (Implemented OpenID Connect, Ruby and Rails version Upgrade)
HYRR	ReactJS, Java Spring, Hibernate, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JQuery	MySQL database	Eclipse IDE, MySQL Workbench 8.0	Software Engineer (Worked as Full Stack, Implemented assessment feature from scratch)

Music Mayhem Trivia	Ruby on Rails, ReactJS, MongoDB, CSS, HTML	Postgres Database	MongoDB, Git, Heroku, Postgres Database, Terminal	Software Engineer (Worked as Full Stack and implemented MongoDB)
Zeehaus	Ruby on Rails, ReactJS, Blockchain, CSS, HTML	Postgres Database	Stellar Blockchain, Git, Heroku, Postgres Database, Terminal	Software Engineer (Worked as Full Stack and Implemented Cryptocurrency Exchange with Blockchain Technology)
Lucknow Metro Services	JSP, Servlet, HTML, CSS etc.	MySQL Server DataBase	Eclipse IDE, MySQL WorkBench 6.0	College Project with Team
Lucknow Metro Rail Corporation	Core Java	MySQL	Eclipse IDE, MYSQL WorkBench 6.0	College Project with Team
Library Management System	Core Java	MySQL	NetBeans IDE, MySQL Oracle 10g	College Project Individual
Virtual Calculator	Core Java	None	Eclipse IDE	College Project Individual
Screen Saver	Core Java	None	Eclipse IDE	College Project Individual

Awards and Achievements

- ❖ GATE 2019 QUALIFIED
- Certificate of AWS Cloud Practitioner Essentials from AWS Training and Certification.
- Certificate of JAVA TECHNOLOGIES from CDAC Mohali, Punjab.
- Certificate of CORE JAVA from Cetpa Infotech Pvt Ltd, Lucknow.
- Certificate of Entrepreneurship Workshop from AKTU, Lucknow.
- ❖ 10000 Rupees Awarded in B.Tech for securing 80.66%.

Technical Skills

- Technologies (Ruby on Rails, ReactJS, Java SE, EE, Spring, Hibernate, JSP, C, C++)
- Deployment(Heroku, Jenkins, Netlify)
- Database (MySQL, PostgresQL, PHPMyAdmin, MongoDB)
- Cloud Service(AWS)
- Web Designing(HTML, CSS, Java Script, JQuery, Bootstrap)
- Tools(Docker, EclipseIDE, Linux)
- Agile Development Tools (JIRA, ASANA)
- Other Know Technologies(Stellar Blockchain, Hyperledger)

Ankur Gupta

Personal Interests

Cricket, Listening Music, Traveling, Reading Books

Declaration

I, Ankur Gupta, hereby declare that the information contained herein is true and correct to the best of my knowledge and belief.



Signature: